Hello.
In this next section of the course, we're going to go over how to create a boss battle.
The first thing we're going to do is create a new level where we're going to fight our boss.
So if we go to file and go new level, select basic, then go create, then save this level and save
it inside of our level folder.
I just call this our boss map.
Next, let's design a new toolset for our boss level.
So I'm going to go to my task order and right click and go people to the top map.
And I'll just call this my boss, Tom.
If we open it up.
And go to active.
Toss that and set the toss.
Set.
Toss it.
I'm just going to adjust my map with something like.
22.
And I'll make my map height.
Ten.
I may need to change these later, but for now we'll have these values.
I'm then going to make my tall width and my tall height.
16.
Next.
I'm just going to drag in this platform and place it on the ground.
I'm now just going to quickly design an arena for my boss level.
Okay, So this is the map that I'm going to have for my boss level Make something similar to this.
We don't want to do designed.
We just kind of want an arena.
Then we can close this and go add go basic and select player start.
If we go to the wild settings, go to the game mode and make sure it's our two D game mode and place
our boss tor map behind our paper character.
Okay, so I'm just going to expand the size of this.
I'll make it 13 and delete my law.
And I'll just make it to my player.
Character fits within this tone map.
So I think this is a good size.
If we go back to level one and just copy and paste the background here.
So I'm just going to copy this and paste this background in my bus map.
I'm just going to adjust my Bus Tom app so that there is a bit more ground.
Okay, so now we have finished designing the arena for our boss level.